Hello everyone.
I'm Yuri Kobashi.
I'm Haruka Kuromi.
I'm Yuna Shibata.
I'm Hazuki Mukai.
Where are we now?
The sea is beautiful.
We're here at Cape Muroto in Kochi Prefecture.
We've come all the way to Kochi.
Shikoku. But the reason why we are here in Kochi today is...
We are here in Kochi to carry out the project "Nogizaka46's Dream Comes True".
It's been a while since our last visit, but we are still working on it.
This time, we would like to commemorate the one millionth subscriber to our NogizakaDistributing Channel by making your dreams come true in the third installment of our project!
Out of about 12,000 submissions, the dream that we will be helping with this time is....
Manamin, a 19-year-old college freshman.
I left my parents to play baseball in high school.
I played baseball at Muroto High School in Kochi Prefecture.
I am looking forward to working with the Nogizaka46 Nogizaka Baseball Team to promote Muroto High School and women's baseball.
I would like to help promote Muroto High School and women's baseball with the Nogizaka46 Nogizaka Baseball Club!
I would like to give something back to the juniors who have been with me through the dark years.
I received a letter from them saying that they would be very happy if they could lend me a helping hand.
I wonder if I will be able to meet the current high school students if you mean the juniors.
I wonder if I can meet them.
First of all, I'd like to meet Mr. Manamin.
Of course.
Maybe a little.
Are there any juniors?
I wonder if she's here.
They're already here at Cape Muroto.
Will we see him? Can we meet him?
Let's go find Mr. Manamin.
Let's go.
Let's go!
So, first of all, I was walking around looking for Manamin who applied for the job.
Oh, no, no, no. Manamin?
Yes, that's right. Hello.
Sorry it's taken so long.
This is Manami Fujimoto who applied this time.
Thank you so much for your application.
May I ask again what your dream is?
Yes, I want to promote the Muroto High School girls' official baseball team and women's baseball.
By the way, what kind of club is the Muroto High School girls' baseball club that you used to play in?
It is one of the few public high schools in Japan that has a girls' baseball club.
Girls who wanted to play baseball came from all over the country.
When I was a freshman, we had only one member.
When I was a junior, we had nine members, and now we have about 15.
The Muroto High School Girls Baseball Club was on the verge of distribution soon after Manami joined the club due to a decline in the number of members.
I wanted to return the favor to the juniors who saved us from such a crisis.
Manami decided to apply this time.
The four of them will join the Muroto High School students as club members for a day and help convey the appeal of women's baseball to them.
to help convey the appeal of women's baseball.
By the way, do the people at Muroto High School know we're coming?
Well, the advisor knows, but...
But the club members don't know that we're coming.
What am I going to do?
I wonder if they'll understand.
I think they'll be fine... if they're so assertive.
It says 46.
I'm so nervous. Oh, I'm so excited!
Will the surprise be a success?
Let's go meet the girls' baseball team who are practicing at school!
This is Muroto High School, isn't it?
Excuse me for interrupting.
What was the school like?
It's a small school, less than 100 students.
The girls come from all over.
We live in a dormitory.
Do you come here often after you graduate?
I've only been here once since I graduated.
So it's been a while.
It's been a while.
It's nice to be here.
How do you feel now?
How do I feel now?
Interview.
This is the baseball field.
Is this it?
This is it.
It's okay.
He's here.
They're here.
Is it okay?
Yes.
We're nervous.
Do any of you know who we are?
There's one girl I like a lot.
How much do you like one person?I think you know how much I like each of you.
I think you know.
But it's okay.
Go with confidence.
I'm going to put on a face that says I'm a really cute idol.
Sparkle!
They won't notice.
Don't notice
I don't notice
Nervous
I'm nervous.
No, Manami, you're nervous, too.
It hurts
It hurts.
Probably just as exciting.
Yes, I'm sure.
I don't know if you noticed.
I hope you noticed.
I wonder if she noticed.
Say hello... louder.
Seinogasa de...
Hello.
Who's there? Who's there?
Let's go!
Excuse me, sir, I'm practicing.Excuse me, sir, we're practicing.
I'm practicing.
Excuse me, excuse me, I'm practicing.
Excuse me while I'm practicing.
Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
Excuse me for interrupting your practice.
Would you like to say hello?
Shall I say hello?
Nice to meet you. Excuse me.
We're from the Nogizaka baseball team.
Pleased to meet you.
It's a long way.
Too far away
The surprise was a success!
I decided to explain the project to the club members once again.
We at Nogizaka Delivering Nogizaka were looking for a project to make everyone's dreams come true.
Manami-san, an OG of the baseball club here in Nogizaka, applied for the project and we decided to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I'm here on a moment's notice.
I was dressed like this.
I came dressed like this.
Do you know Nogizaka?
Yes, I do.
I'm so glad.
I was running around the most when I heard that there's a man here who really likes Nogizaka.I heard earlier that there is one person who really likes Nogizaka, Manami-san, and I was wondering if he was the one who was running away the most.
It's easy to tell, isn't it?
He was the only one who was a little different from the others, so I was happy to see him.
I was so happy.
I'm going to ask you something.
I'll stop.
Just so you know, don't get your hopes up.
Don't get your hopes up.
Just in case.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Are there any diapers here?
Are there any diapers?
I like them all.
Yes, I like them all.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Yes, Sirna.
Oh, wow.
Lunapi.
I am very sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Now I'm going to take Lunapi with me.
And so, although we are still a little nervous, four of us have decided to join the club temporarily for a day!
I'm so happy!
We'll start by pairing up and playing catch.
Let's play catch!
Oh, wow!
Wow! Great!!!
I'm so happy! Catch!
Boat!
Too much fun!
What year are you in high school?
I'm a sophomore.
Sophomore year?
Wow! That's awesome! He's so cool!
The black guy talks so much.
No way!
Nakano-san, Chikamoto-san and Kinami-san are my favorite duo.
Yes! Please!
Morishita-san.
Surely you've joined Samurai De Pon.
Yes.
As expected of the members of the Nogizaka Baseball Club.
We're going to keep going as far as the other members.
Thank you. Even your name.
Don't worry, Saeki-san.
I can't reach him at all.
I'm sorry.
I'm about to get blistered.
Yay!
I'll only have you play catch with me.
Otherwise, I'm not going home.
Wow!
Oh, my God.
Smell, smell. Smell. Smell. Smell.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I like it.
Aoboro-Seriously
Sorry. Thank you.
It's hard to smell.
I turned around and said, "Excuse me, sir, there were flowers here.
They smelled so good.
I'm a new student starting today.
It's Shi-chan!
Shi-chan!
Did you start acting in high school?
No, I started in second grade.
I didn't know that. That's great.
That's why you're so cool.
You're really good.
Not at all.
It's hard to believe you're a beginner.
He can catch and throw the ball like a beginner. It's amazing.
I'm a fan from today.
It's a shame I didn't know about him before.
He's so good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Chibara, chibara, chibara!
I'm Asuke.
I want you to teach me.
I want to improve.
I'll teach youI'll teach you.
Please.
With the current members of the baseball team
Catching the ball
How did the four of you do after this valuable experience?
How did you like it? Catching the ball.
What? The way you threw from so close.
From our point of view, you were pros.
No, really.
The strength of the pitch when it hit the ground.
It was amazing.
It was like a slam!
It's good.
And it stretches.
It's amazing, isn't it?
And to be able to catch a ball from this distance...
It's not often you get to play catch from this distance.
It was fresh.
How was it?
You were really good at catching the ball, weren't you?
Yes.
When you made a mistake, you handled it like a shortstop.
The way he handled it.
He even took bounces.
That saved me a lot.
We're going to take a break here.
I'd like to take a break and talk with you all.
How long have you been an idol?
I'm 24 now.I'm 24 now.
I'm down to about 17.
Second year of high school?
That's right.
I joined in my second year of high school.
Oh, really?
I joined at the end of my freshman year.
I'm 19 now.
Really?
I wonder if I can still do it.
Can I still do it?
Yes, I think so.
You're in your first year of high school, right?
I joined in the first year of high school.
How can you be so cute?
They're all pretty.
They're all cute.
Too bad.
I like to see girls playing sports.
They're all so cute!
They're so cute!
They're so cute and cool.
I don't think we can get this cuteness out of them.
I know.
Just looking at them makes me smile.
What's your fondest memory from high school?
Oh, memories.
I wasn't allowed to take my cell phone to school.
I joined this group and transferred.I got into this group, and then I transferred out of school.
The day before I got in, the day before the acceptance announcement, I was ready to be pissed off.
I took a picture with my classmates.
Ew...
That's my favorite memory.
That's amazing.
I have a private school meeting the day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow?
In Tokyo.
I was supposed to go home today.
But they said it's for some reason.
I wondered why, but he said I should come to the club activities.
Thank you for going that far.
Thank you very much.
Sensei.
You're really moving me.
Thank you very much.
I like you.
We all know each other.
You and the teacher get along so well.
That's amazing.
That's not true.
You look like you're having a lot of fun talking to the teachers.
When you first joined the school, you came alone and worked with him.
That's what you said you were doing.
So you're like a mentor to him.
Even if you didn't say what was bothering you at school...
Even if I didn't talk about it.
I was able to ask him for advice.I was able to ask for a little advice there, and it helped to lighten my heart.
I was able to lighten my heart.
I am very grateful to her.
I can cry a lot.
I can cry, I can cry, I can cry
I can cry
It's a very good story.
What do you like about him?
I'm sure you'd like to hear about it.
Everybody don't shut up
Let's think about it.
Let's all think about it.
When he took off his glasses, he said he had big eyes.
I want to see them, I want to see them, I want to see them.
I don't want to show you.
I showed you.
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it.
They're huge.
It's not even close.
That's too close.
Wait, that's the first one.
That's the first one.
It's hard to say.
The tension is easing, and we're getting closer and closer.
Come on, let's do it together.
What are we going to practice next?
Next, we'll do seat-knocking for each position.
After that, we'll have them watch us practice together.
Let's see if we can do that.
We'll take our positions, too. We're about the position, too.
I've never done it before.
Can you do it?
Yes, we can.
I've never knocked.
First, I'd like to observe you knocking.
Bon appétit.
Oh!
I'll go all one.
Yes, sir
Oh!
I won. I won.
Just kidding.
Cut Cut
Right, right.
I don't know where to throw.
First and third base.
Right, right.
What do we do?
We can't do this.
Wait.
You're cool.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Wow.Whoa.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
That's so cool!
The four of us are excited to see the power of knocking up close.
Well, I'd like to invite you all to join us.
Can you do it?
And here's a suggestion from the teacher.
Since Muroto High School and Nogizaka-san are going to be performing together...
"Since Muroto High School and Nogizaka-san are going to do this together, let's do 46 knocks together.
Let's do it as if it's the end.
Is that alright with you?
I look forward to working with you.
46 knocks to success!
We're united by our engines.
Let's make it 46!
100 million times, even if you lose
I'm...
First step, please
Step one.
Please
Please, please
Please.
Go. Go.
Go.
Come on.
Come on.Come on.
Please.
Come on.
please.
Second, please.
Please.
Come on.
Oh, my God!
Strong!
Oh!
Ooh!
Thirty-three!
Come on!
It's hard!
Hard!
Go!
Ooh!
Ooh!Ooh!
It is
Yes.
The high school students were so happy to see Nogizaka-san at the event.
I think they were able to see how fun and exciting it is to be a part of a women's baseball game.
I think we were able to convey the fun and charm of women's baseball in a good way.
It was fun!
Please give me the 43rd one!
Yuna's sword is moving!
It's okay! Yuna, it's okay!
This is baseball.
Let's get it, let's get it, just like this.
Nice!
Finally!
45, please.
Wow!
I'm scared!
This could be bad.
Forty-four.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
45, please.
Forty-five.
Wow!
That's not even close.
I'll take it.
Forty-four.
I can do it.
And finally, the 46th one.And finally the 46th one!
Yay, yay, yay!
Yeah?
Come on, come on, come on.
Wow.
Yay.
Yay!
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
Yay, Melodee! Yay! 46, 46, 46! Yay!
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
The last four were tough. I wish I could've gotten them.
You were so strict, like a baseball team. It was a little standoffish, but it was fun.
It was fun. I don't want to end. I don't want to end.
I don't want it to end.
How was your day, Mr. Hanami? How was the day?
I had a great day with Nogizaka-san and the Muroto High girls' baseball team.
We had a lot of fun.
I think we were able to convey the fun and appeal of women's baseball to the YouTube viewers.
I am very happy that we were able to get 46 knocks in the end.
Thank you very much!
So, Mr. Hanami, were you able to make your dream come true?
We did, thank you very much!
It was a really fun day!
Thank you so much to everyone!
Mr. Hanami
Good friends
Muroto High School
Great!Great.
Thank you for watching!